When it comes to cleaning up...
I'm very thorough!
Bodyguard & Maid,
Previously in Prince Osvalt's Service
Lena
Indeed, in all respects...
We must be flawless!
That is a butler's job.
Bodyguard, Butler & Former Knight,
Previously in Prince Osvalt's Service
Leonardo
Parnacorta is famous for the
excellence of its chivalric order.
Prepare to die!
Perhaps they instruct even their
butlers and maids in martial arts.
No, They're Just Weird
But even then...
These two are really tough.
The Too-Perfect Saint: Tossed Aside
by My Fiancé and Sold to Another Kingdom
Saint Philia!
Episode 3
"Our First Date"
The cleaning's all done!
Excellent work. You're both phenomenal.
Oh, hardly.
The monsters were already weakened
due to the holy sanctuary.
Besides...
Extremely
Effective
Mental Image
That potion you gave me makes me
feel like I'm back in my heyday!
Plus, look at how dark
and full my hair has gotten!
I'm feeling on the top of my game, too!
You're amazing, Saint Philia!
It was just a rudimentary potion, though...
Actually, I've been wondering something.
What have you been jotting down?
Oh, this?
I'm recording information on the location,
scale, and ferocity of monster outbreaks.
It sure does seem like
they've been on the rise, huh?
Even when we wipe them out,
they come back in no time.
What's up with that?
Well, you see...
In addition to the surface world
which we humans inhabit,
there exist the Demon Realm and Heaven.
Monsters are native to the Demon Realm,
but sometimes a portion of them
make it up here to the surface.
Just a portion? But there's been so many...
Yes. The more nests in the Demon Realm,
the more monsters there are,
which in turn means more
and more frequent surface invasions.
Saint Philia.
The carriage is ready.
Let's return to the mansion.
Yes, ma'am!
By the way, Saint Philia,
we're done for the day now, right?
Yes. What of it?
In that case...
Prince Osvalt!
Good to see you!
Highness! Take some of my vegetables!
Sure, I'll stop by later.
Oh, out on business now?
Yeah.
I'm off on a date.
A d-date?!
Miss Philia!
I tried to come ea—
Sorry. Guess I kept you waiting.
Not at all.
Let's make it a date!
A d-date?
I've heard the word before,
but I don't know what it entails.
For today, how about a tour of Almburg?
Don't worry! I'll make sure to bring a guide!
A guide?
Why is my guide Prince Osvalt?
I'm honored to be given
the role of escorting our saint.
Let me show you around Almburg!
This is the merchant quarter.
If you're in the market for anything,
this should be your first stop.
Monster attacks have actually made it hard
to leave the city for the past few months.
But that's all in the past now thanks to you.
Everyone's so happy the city's thriving again.
I'm happy, too.
All because of you.
Thank you so much.
He thanked me?
I've just been doing my job...
Why does it feel like my heart's racing?
Is something the matter?
Oh, nothing!
Hey, it's the saint!
Saint Philia?
I had no idea you were in Parnacorta...
I know you, don't I?
Yes.
I made an appeal to you
once back in Girtonia.
Thanks to you, I've been
able to keep up my trade.
This is my son. Say hello.
Hello.
Oh, no. I'm going to scare someone again.
Thank you, Saint Philia.
My dad was real sad that he
couldn't work for so long.
So thanks a bunch!
Y-You're... welcome?
Thanks!
It's the saint!
Thank you so much for coming to Parnacorta!
Coming all the way from Girtonia...
They're feeding you well, right?
U-Um...
Let's go.
Sorry, everyone! I've got dibs for today!
Good job, Your Highness!
Sorry I startled you.
It's not much by way of apology,
but please order anything you'd like.
The desserts here are delicious.
What's your favorite kind?
My favorite?
"Whatever's edible" mindset
If you're not sure, may I
make some recommendations?
Oh, yes. Please do.
Th-This is all so alien.
How am I to act in this situation?
Miss Philia...
Let me thank you again for all
the effort you've put in this week.
But I've also received reports
that you're overworking yourself.
Miss Philia, rest is also part of the job.
That's... part of my job?
I think you should take
more time for yourself.
To that end...
Tell me more about you.
What you like, what you dislike,
your interests... Anything.
I want to know not just our saint,
but Philia Adenauer herself.
My!
I don't know how to respond to that.
After all...
I've never had space to have my
own thoughts about anything.
I wasn't really allowed to.
What a fine, calming aroma...
Of course.
I like tea.
I guess that's okay.
But I can't tell you more,
because I really don't know.
Then let's feel it out little by little.
I know! Is there anywhere
you'd like to go next?
I'll take you anywhere you want.
Well... may I make a request?
Here we go!
Might I have permission to read the
restricted books in the castle library?
What are you trying to find out?
The sheer quantity of monsters
appearing in Parnacorta lately
can't be explained merely by geography
and the prior absence of a saint.
A similar phenomenon was beginning
in Girtonia just before I came here.
This sudden surge in monsters...
I've seen such happenings chronicled
in old Girtonian history books.
You seem to have similar records.
If my hypothesis is correct,
the Demon Realm is approaching the surface.
So you're saying...
What, exactly?
Oh, that's right. I guess I have to explain!
Saint Philia... this is nowhere near a date!
The Too-Perfect Saint: Tossed Aside
by My Fiancé and Sold to Another Kingdom
Four hundred years ago,
there was a time the Demon Realm
came close to the surface world.
Monsters invaded us, running rampant.
The archdemon Asmodeus took
advantage of the chaos
to rise from the depths of the
Demon Realm and come to the surface.
Humans and animals were
slaughtered en masse,
and many kingdoms faced
the threat of destruction.
But just then...
A saint rose up to oppose Asmodeus.
Her name was Fianna Aesfill,
and she would later be known
as Archsaint Fianna.
She created massive barriers to purge
the monsters in the blink of an eye,
then separated Asmodeus's soul
from his supposedly invincible body
and sealed it away.
Thus, peace was restored to the land
and history continues to this day.
You're saying we're facing
another such crisis?
Yes. I believe it's highly likely.
The prince called a full conference
in response to my supposition.
He's asking for the opinions
of others as well...
What precisely happens as
the Demon Realm gets closer?
The spawning of monsters will likely
increase between ten and twentyfold.
T-Twentyfold?!
It's hard enough to keep
them at bay as it is!
Yes.
Which means the pillars of light
may no longer be enough.
So we'll have to call in the military?
But to increase our defense budget
based on such thin speculation...
He's right.
It's natural they wouldn't believe a girl
from another kingdom who only just arrived.
Know your place, woman! It's shameful!
All right. Let's see if tripling
the defense budget does the trick.
B-But our budget this year
is already so tight—
Budgets are just budgets.
Let's talk my father and my brother into it.
But—
I'm hoping this is all unnecessary, of course.
But it's better to be prepared
than to regret it later.
I'll take responsibility for everything.
I'm putting my full faith behind Miss Philia.
She's done so much for us, after all.
It's only polite to pay
her back with our trust.
Any objections?
How can he be so confident?
Is he not afraid of rebuke?
Even if he's royalty, there must surely be
consequences for wasting treasury funds...
Is there any way I can help him?
These are the forces and locations
we can rally on short notice.
Will this do?
It's not nearly enough.
What?!
This will spell a great deal of casualties.
That's rough...
We only have so many soldiers.
There's a way to do this.
But if I go through with it...
My priority right now
is protecting the people of Parnacorta.
There's something else we can try.
We could erect a Great Purification
Circle over the entire kingdom.
A Great Purification Circle?!
B-But that's an ancient ritual.
Without mastery of archaic languages and
full understanding of several spell lineages...
I can do it.
This magic circle doesn't have the caging
properties of a standard barrier.
It's fully focused on weakening monsters.
Standard Barrier
Great Purification Circle
Its purifying power will allow any within it
to be disposed of with ease.
However...
Is there a catch?
Yes.
To erect a Great Purification Circle,
I must remain at its center,
acting as the ritual's core.
Capital City
Almburg
(Current location)
Effectively, I will have
to remain in the capital.
In other words, I...
I won't be able to do most of
the jobs I've been performing so far.
Er... is that all?
Yes?
Well, that sounds great, then!
You work too hard as it is!
Actually, will maintaining the ritual
be exhausting in its own right?
No, once successfully activated,
it shouldn't prove draining at all.
Then this sounds like the perfect solution!
Looks like you're saving our
kingdom yet again, Miss Philia.
What's wrong? You look unhappy.
Is something else weighing on your mind?
Well, I...
I'm thinking of my sister back home.
Miss Mia?
Yes.
She's an excellent saint,
but she has no knowledge of ancient rituals.
She won't be able to create
a Great Purification Circle.
And you're worried about her?
Ah, p-please forgive me, Your Highness.
I'm Parnacorta's saint. I shouldn't be...
No need to apologize.
What kind of big sister wouldn't be worried?
Don't hold back.
You can help her out.
In that case...
May I...
May I send her a letter?
I simply can't accept this!
My sister would never leave the
kingdom without a word to me!
Mother and Father insist
that it's what she wanted.
Which means...
I should ask her fiancé,
Prince Julius, about it.
They say he wept as he watched her go, so...
Prince Julius.
I believe you wanted to see me?
What do you—
Mia Adenauer!
Will you please become my wife?
Huh?!
Such beauty! Such grace!
You're a more than worthy bride
for the second prince of Girtonia!
What in the world is he talking about?
On the heels of losing his fiancée,
he's already proposing to another girl?
And her little sister, at that?
How absolutely disgusting.
Wait...
If Philia marries the prince,
we'll get in good with the court!
You could say she's finally
doing right by the family!
The reason they're both so
indifferent to her departure...
Did they know about this?
Come on! Let's have your answer!
In your dreams.
But if I want to know what really happened,
I need to get him to tell me.
I have to do this!
Mia?
Highness...
Please give me some time to think it over.
My sister's only just departed.
I surely couldn't agree to marry so soon.
R-Right, of course.
I suppose I've been a bit hasty, haven't I?
In that case, let's give it some time.
I can't afford to cross him just yet.
I have to suppress my true feelings.
It wouldn't do to accept
the proposal so quickly.
I'll distract him, throw him off,
and draw out the information I want.
I'm not strategically minded at all...
But for my sister, I'll do whatever I must!
I'm simply delighted, Your Highness!
If he thinks I'm nothing
but sunshine and smiles,
he's got another thing coming!
That was the day I began
my investigation in earnest.
In my father's study,
I found plans for a new mansion
and a pile of contract documents.
In my mother's room,
I found a new box of jewelry.
Philia was such a bore to be around!
I grit my teeth through dates
to get on the prince's good side,
all while keeping up my saintly duties.
The monsters are only increasing
in number with my sister gone.
It's taking everything I have
to stave them off.
But...
I'll do the best I can.
Big Sister...
What in the world is taking Mia so long?
What if His Highness changes his mind?
From Philia
Please. No need to worry there.
Today's the day I'll lower
his guard and get him to talk.
Marquess Adenauer's quite
a wily one, isn't he?
He offloaded a burden, made a tidy profit,
and earned a peerage in the process!
And didn't he and Prince Julius look tickled
concocting that plan to sell Saint Philia off?
I know our old saint was utterly obnoxious...
But how sad to think her fiancé
and parents hated her, too!
What are they talking about?
Impressive that they pulled it off
while the king was laid up sick.
The marquess was handsomely
rewarded, wasn't he?
He's apparently using that
to fund a new estate.
Some men get all the luck!
It's all coming together.
They sold my sister...
I wanted to believe that my
parents were good people.
I had my questions about
the way they treated my sister.
But I...
I was afraid to see the truth,
so I blinded myself!
Big Sister!
Have you lived your whole life
in a world this cold to you?
I'm sorry...
I'm sorry, Philia!
Is today the day you finally accept my offer?
Your Highness...
Did my sister really go
to Parnacorta of her own free will?
Do we have to go over this again?
Philia chose to break
our engagement and leave.
Just what you'd expect from her, right?
She loves nothing more
than showing off her talents!
I already had my hands full
with the terrible way she carried on.
I mean, I was her fiancé!
I was the one getting all the complaints!
Meanwhile, Mia, you just focus on
your saintly duties instead of
sticking your nose where it doesn't belong.
Everyone loves your beauty
and your charming smile!
I happen to believe that you're really
the greatest saint of all time.
I went along with them giving
that title to Philia,
but she's fatally lacking in charm!
Have faith in yourself!
You've already surpassed her!
Right.
Hey, don't worry.
Philia's the saint of a neighboring
kingdom, living her new life!
I'm sure she'd want her
dear younger sister to be happy!
Highness...
I accept your proposal!
Really?!
Yes!
I'll get engaged to this man.
Yes, of course you do!
I'll take him to the heights of ecstasy,
give him a long leash,
and then, when I deem the time to be right...
I'll betray him.
After all, he has to be punished
for betraying my sister.
That's how it has to be.
The Too-Perfect Saint: Tossed Aside by
My Fiancé and Sold to Another Kingdom.
Next time, episode 4:
Next Time
Episode 4
"Feelings Entrusted"
"Feelings Entrusted."